<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts -</title><link>https://javrin.github.io/posts/</link><description>All Posts |</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>j4vr1n.harmonics471@dralias.com (Jonas Avrin)</managingEditor><webMaster>j4vr1n.harmonics471@dralias.com (Jonas Avrin)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 13:30:42 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://javrin.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Trying Out Pages CMS - A New CMS for GitHub</title><link>https://javrin.github.io/posts/2024-02-23-trying-out-pages-cms-a-new-cms-for-github/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 13:30:42 -0500</pubDate><author>Jonas Avrin</author><guid>https://javrin.github.io/posts/2024-02-23-trying-out-pages-cms-a-new-cms-for-github/</guid><description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;ve been investigating solutions for CMS but haven&rsquo;t jumped into anything, until today, and who can blame me with the number of solutions sprouting up daily it seems. There&rsquo;s decapcms which I&rsquo;ve known about since day 1, the gran-daddy you might say.
cms distinction decapcms Previously Netlify staticcms Fork of Decap focused on core features sveltia-cms Decap&rsquo;s backend with a prettier skin statamic Full-stack SSG and CMS I&rsquo;m currently using Obsidian as a local CMS solution which is more than capable but I feel the content creation process could be more efficient and accessible from more devices.]]></description></item><item><title>👋 Hello Hugo!</title><link>https://javrin.github.io/posts/2023-08-30-hello-hugo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 16:55:18 -0400</pubDate><author>Jonas Avrin</author><guid>https://javrin.github.io/posts/2023-08-30-hello-hugo/</guid><description>Photo by Chris Barbalis on Unsplash
👋 Hello Hugo This is my new site generated using Hugo!
Ahhhh ☺ &amp;ndash; a fresh start. A new chapter is beginning, and I&amp;rsquo;ve had my eye on Hugo for a while. Having started and abandoned SSG (static site generator) projects in the past, this might be thee one for a while. It feels stable, feature rich, and easy to work with&amp;ndash;all characteristics that are crucial for consistently keeping up and growing a website.</description></item></channel></rss>